# Michalis Mavromatakis

Senior Full-Stack Developer

#### **Contact**

**Address** 

**Athens** 

Phone

0030 6959783619

E-mail

michamav19@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/michalis-mavromatakis

#### **Technical Profile**

#### **Excellent:**

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Typescript, PHP
- MySQL, GIT

#### Good:

- NextJs, NodeJS,
- Express, Java
- AWS, MongoDB
- Figma
- WordPress
- Windows, MacOS, Linux,
- Office, LibreOffice

# **Competencies**

Project Management

**Technical Analysis** 

**Software Best Practices** 

Agile Workflow

Experienced Senior Full Stack Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the software engineer with knowledge of complete product lifecycle through requirements, analysis, data modeling, design, development, testing, documentation and delivery of projects. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Department of Management Science and Technology from Athens University of Economics and Business.

## **Work History**

2022-09 -Current

## **Senior Full-Stack Developer**

FlexCar, Athens

- Front-End: ReactJs, NextJs, TypeScript
- Back-End: NodeJs, Express
- Databases: MongoDB, AWS (TimeStream, S3)
- AWS: ECR, ECS, Fargate, Amplify, CloudWatch
- Git: Github, CI-CD workflows

2021-06 -2022-08

## **Lead Full Stack Developer**

Collegelink, Athens

Day to Day Responsibilities:

- Design and implement full-stack projects
- Check team members' task progress with agile project management method
- Delegate work and assignments to team members
- Weekly meetings with team members for career roadmaps to improve hard & soft skills
- Weekly code reviews and QA to team members' tasks
- Git & Auto Deployment roadmaps implementations
- Write onboarding and technical documentations

2020-10 -2021-06

# Full Stack Developer at KEPYES/GES

Military of Greece, Athens

For my services to the greek military i worked as Full-Stack Developer:

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, SCSS, ReactJs
- Back-end: PHP Symfony
- DataBase: Oracle DB, SQL
- Programs: Visual Studio Code, WebStorm, PhpStorm, DataGrip
- Other: GitLab, Linux

2018-03 -2020-09

# **Full Stack Developer**

Collegelink, Athens

Team Technologies:

• Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX

Web development projects

**Programming** 

Organization and Time Management

Planning and Coordination

Dependable and Responsible

Teambuilding

• Back-end: PHP

DataBase: Workbench, SQLProject management tool: Jira

• Other: GitKraken, MacOS, Windows, Visual Studio

Code, Figma

### **Education**

Web Design And Front End Developer
Expertise: Web Development

National & Kapodistrian University of Athens -

*E-learning* Grade: 9.4/10

2013-09 - **Bachelor's Degree: Department of**2018-04 **Management Science And Technology** 

Athens University of Economics And Business -

Athens

Grade: 7.1/10

Major in E-Commerce, Innovation and Entrepreneurship Grade: 7.5/10

Minor in Information Systems and Technologies

Grade: 8.2/10

2007-09 - Varvakeio School - Athens

2013-06